A Guide to the Cartoons by Art Wood, 1952-1959, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- DIOGENES No Date
  Search for an honest to goodness issue Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats
- DOWN, BOY, DOWN! No Date
  Chiang's ambitions
- PUBLIC ENEMY NO. 1 No Date
  Careless smoker Parched fields... in Virginia
- PEACEFUL CO-EXISTENCE No Date
  Another United States plane shot down by the Communists (Reds)s
- THE SEA AROUND US No Date
  Jul 26 United States shoots down reds Communists (Reds)s shoot down United States
- HIS CHRISTMAS TREE No Date
  Reckless holiday driver Highways Safety
- I SHALL HOLD MYSELF AT THE DISPOSAL OF FRANCE No Date
  De Gaulle France
- OLD FAITHFUL No Date
  Threats words dramatic spoutings Steel dispute Strikes
- PUBLIC ENEMY NO. 1 No Date
  $ Vote here Frauds Elections
- BOOK ENDS No Date
  Deficiency in United States education indifference lack respect Schools
- THE ONLY PROP No Date
  Hydrogen bomb war Big 4 Allies understanding
- HOME RUN No Date
  Communists (Reds)s The London 9-Power conf Agreement rearmament Germany
- ANCHORS AWEIGH- HEY... No Date
  Blockade Red China Knowland Dulles, John F.
- HE'LL BOUNCE BACK No Date
  Censure blow Joe McCarthy, Joseph
- LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAFTA TO BACK No Date
  North Atlantic Treay Organization (NATO) EDC Road closed Germany United States
- OUT OF THE FRYING PAN- INTO THE FIRE No Date
  Hot August weather Sept.
- SOUTHERN HOSPITALITY? No Date
  W & M Law School celebration Earl Warren, Earl College of William & Mary
- WHEN DOCTORS DISAGREE No Date
  United States Adenauer England France rearmament Germany
- OOPS No Date
  Nationalist attacks Amoy island Communists (Reds) Attacks Quemoy Formosa
- SUMMER SQUALL No Date
  Campaign Oratory United States Elections
- MEETING WILL COME TO ORDER No Date
  Germany unification Big 4 conference Allies
- AND IT USED TO BE FLYING SAUCERS No Date
  Hoover commission- United States Navy fight
- WIDE OPEN SPACES No Date
  segregation ruling interpretation United States Supreme Court
- VACATION TIME No Date
  Adenauer Hawaii Moscow to United States to England
- SPRING CROP No Date
  Indo-china Civil War
- A NEW WALL OF CHINA No Date
  Mutual defense treaty United States Defense & China Chiang
- THEY'RE YOUR BOYS TOO No Date
  United Nations aid freeing United States Prisoners of war Communists (Reds) China
- HIS SEAT No Date
  United Nations Red China 47-nation condemn for jailing United States Prisoners of war airmen
- THE BIG QUESTION No Date
  Censure
- BUMPED No Date
  Political Parties Republican (GOP) program flight high federal revenue taxes cuts Budget
- IT'S FOR YOU No Date
  temporary party unity Eisenhower, Dwight D. Political parties Republican (GOP)
- YET IN THE DARK STREET SHINETH... No Date
  Xmas troubled times Christmas Religion
- CHRISTMAS WRAPPINGS No Date
  City Council $1.94 taxes budget rate
- FIRST IN LINE No Date
  84th Congress show Foreign trade program
- PLAYING IT FOR ALL ITS WORTH No Date
  Propaganda Mao Tse-tung Hammarskjold, Dag visit
- WHO? ME? No Date
  Recommendation for censure McCarthy, Joseph
- JUST HIS DISH! No Date
  World Series Sports Baseball
- ANOTHER IMPORTANT SERIES No Date
  Germany rearmament battle at London World
- BOO No Date
  Dixon-Yates contract charges 6926 United States Security risk eliminations
- IN THE DOGHOUSE No Date
  Secretary Wilson's "Bird Dog" analogy Wilson
- ON THE DOORSTEP No Date
  City Council taxes rate adjustment problem
- HOPING TO LAND THE BIG ONE No Date
  Independent vote Fall campaign Elections
- SENDING OUT A DOVE No Date
  Atoms-for-peace gift to United Nations United States
- TIME OUT! No Date
  McCarthy, Joseph censure battle United States Congress Senators Recess until NOV 29
- WHAT AM I OFFERED? No Date
  Lives of American United States Prisoners of war Red China
- THERE'S A LONG, LONG TRAIL AWINDIN' No Date
  Christmas shopping list
- BUT IT'S SO GOOD FOR YA! No Date
  Truman, Harry S. Eisenhower, Dwight D. Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocratic United States Congress
- BEATING THE SAME OLD DRUM No Date
  Red China recognition Vishinsky
- NEWS ITEM: IKE BEGINS DRIVE FOR VOTES No Date
  Political Parties Republican (GOP) Congressional campaign Elections
- HOME TO ROOST No Date
  McCarthy, Joseph issue Lame Duck session United States Congress
- EXHAUST No Date
  McCarthy, Joseph The Watkins Committee is partisan a lynching
- JUST WHAT WOULD YOU SUGGEST! No Date
  Co-existence is impossible Knowland Russia United States
- MAYBE YOU CAN DO SOMETHNG WITH HIM! No Date
  United Nations Formosa problems
- THE IDES OF MARCH No Date
  Senate Finance Committee $20 tax cut bill United States Congress taxes budget
- I'D BETTER START WITH CONGRESS FIRST No Date
  Subpeona Stassen, Harold disarmament United States Congress
- REALLY ROLLIN' No Date
  Paris Agreements Capitol Hill United States Congress
- STIRRING THINGS UP No Date
  Campaign speeches Eisenhower, Dwight D. Hot politics Elections
- WELL, HERE GOES! No Date
  W. Germany parliament French Assembly Germany Saar France
- SAME OLD HOT AIR No Date
  recession unemployment Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats Eisenhower, Dwight D. Political Parties Republican (GOP)
- HOPE CHEST No Date
  Elections victory Nov 2 Republicans & Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats Political parties Republican (GOP)
- WORKING MATERIALS No Date
  new wing of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts gifts
- BY THE DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT No Date
  House Senate elections votes United States Congress
- HERE BOY, YOU PULL IT! No Date
  Chiang 's ambitions Knowland
- 'CAUSE IT FEELS SO GOOD WHEN I STOP! No Date
  History status of Southern
- HAVE I LEFT ANYTHING OUT? No Date
  Churchill, Sir Winston artist historian soldier...
- A PIECE FOR YOU AND A PIECE FOR ME No Date
  Salary raises for United States Congress Wage increase
- DRINKING IT IN No Date
  Political Parties Republican (GOP) Candidates Eisenhower, Dwight D.'s support
- THE DAWN OF A NEW DAY No Date
  Peaceful use of Atomic energy World Atoms-for-peace
- TACKS IN THE CHAIR No Date
  South East Asia Treaty Organization (SEATO) Opposition by India, Burma, Ceylon ...
- STANDING PAT No Date
  Nationalist China Matsu
- TICKER TAPE No Date
  Senatorial investigation
- TIED UP TOGETHER No Date
  politics $20 taxes reduction compromise
- CASUALTY No Date
  Communists (Reds) buildup in Korea Armistice agreement
- THE END OF THE ROAD No Date
  Malenkov
- SETTING OUR SIGHTS No Date
  fight if necessary ratified Formosa defense
- THE BRAVE NEW WORLD No Date
  tests A city smashed by the super Atomic bombs
- STRONGER SOVIET TIES No Date
  Communists (Reds) China - Russia treaty 5th anniversary
- AND HOW ABOUT SOME OF YOUR FUNDS No Date
  market in Shockoe Valley
- BOOK WORM No Date
  Virginia manual for teachers Schools Socialist propaganda Education
- PUTTING ON A LITTLE WEIGHT No Date
  City Council budget increase
- ROUND 2 No Date
  Bricker amendment Second senate hearing United States Congress
- AIR MAIL No Date
  8.8% postal pay wage increase $178 million to taxpayers taxes
- OUT OF THE WOODS No Date
  Foreign trade bill High tariffs advocates lobby
- A PLACE IN THE SUN No Date
  Western nations Germany Membership in NATO North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) Allies
- PLAYING BOTH SIDES OF THE FENCE No Date
  Tito Western aid Belgrade talks Foreign aid
- IN THERE SWINGING No Date
  Plans for a nationwide tour Eisenhower, Dwight D. Political Parties Republican (GOP) game
- FOR WHOM THE BELL TOLLS No Date
  Over 630 deaths in Virginia speeder Highways Safety
- FIRE ONE- FIRE TWO- FIRE THREE No Date
  Pay raises: congress, postal... wage increase United States Congress United States Postal Service
- TRYING TO MAKE A MOUNTAIN OF A MOLEHILL No Date
  Dixon-Yates issue
- HERE'S YOUR HAT HERE'S YOUR BAGS WHAT'S YOUR HURRY? No Date
  United States Milk commission.
- DOING A LITTLE BURNING HIMSELF No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. blasts McCarthy, Joseph
- THE WORLD IS WAITING FOR THE SUNRISE No Date
  United States elections returns
- FALL OUT No Date
  Yalta papers on Harriman Yalta papers on Roosevelt, Franklin D....
- FACE TO FACE No Date
  Proposed taxes cuts Mounting United States Defense costs
- WHO'S DRIVING? No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. road plan Opposition Stanley Byrd, Harry F., Sr. Highways
- BACK ON THE MAIN ROAD No Date
  elections detour ends United States Bus. as usual
- SHIPS THAT PASS IN THE NIGHT No Date
  Communists (Reds)'s bombing of Chiang China
- ON TOP OF OLD SMOKEY No Date
  overoptimism summit talks
- AND HOW ARE THINGS IN INDOCHINA? No Date
  Bao Dai Farouk Indo-china
- THIS IS YOUR LATEST WEATHER REPORT No Date
  Hurricane Connie hits Weather
- SCHOOL DAZE No Date
  overcrowded schools
- I STILL LIKE THAT CONSERVATIVE STYLE [Alternate: THAT CONSERVATIVE SUIT SEEMS TO HAVE GONE OUT OF STYLE] No Date
  Elections The Eden tweed British
- CANCELLED No Date
  Veto To John Q. United StatesA White House postal pay wage increase United States Postal Service
- RINGING THE BELL No Date
  drive to abolish polio your contribution
- BOGGED DOWN No Date
  state highways plans $100 billion Federal road plan
- SLOW AND BY NO MEANS SURE No Date
  United Nations Release of United States prisoners of war in China
- SPIKE No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D.'s endorsement Rumor of Benson 's ouster
- QUESTION FOR A COMING GENERATION No Date
  Effects of Super-bomb tests Atomic bombs
- CHECK UP No Date
  Atomic radiation National Academy of Scientists AEC United States Atomic Energy Commission (AEC)
- FUSE No Date
  4th of July death toll Carelessness on the highways safety
- HOLD STILL LITTLE SHAD- I WON'T HURT YOU... No Date
  Communists (Reds) China Formosa
- LOOKING AHEAD No Date
  Germany Communists (Reds)'s proposal to end occupation Russia
- MORE THAN A CHINESE KITE! No Date
  Communists (Reds) airpower buildup China Formosa
- HE DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS LOADED No Date
  anti-communist blasts Communists (Reds)s Bandung
- NOW, MEET MY FRIEND No Date
  Virginia state income tax deadline May 1 form 1040 taxes
- AND THE WALLS CAME TUMBLING DOWN No Date
  reduced tariffs trade barriers Foreign trade
- THE FISH THAT GOT AWAY No Date
  West german neutrality Communists (Reds)s Germany
- READY FOR THE HEAP No Date
  United States Milk Commission Consumer opposition producer
- DOWN BOY, DOWN! No Date
  over-optimism at...talks Eisenhower, Dwight D. Big 4 plans
- THE TIE THAT BINDS No Date
  Communist philosophy Tito Khrushchev, Nikita